生命周期的一个关键点是 你的应用要一直运行
A key takeaway from life cycles is that your application runs until Android
直到Android系统需要释放资源或者别的什么时候
needs to free resources or something else.
这就意味着，我们设计Sunshine 去一直很好地运行
That means, it's best if we design Sunshine to continue to work well even
甚至当操作系统不得不关闭我们的app，并且我们的app不再有天气数据
if the operating system has to close us and the app no longer has weather data.
有人可能会问，这是云连接的错
One might ask, this is the error of the connected cloud.
我们不需要总是去抓取数据
Why don't we just always fetch t
我们真的需要考虑在设备上存储一切吗？
Do we really need to worry about saving anything on the device?
好了，首先，用户体验是重要的
Well, first, user experience is important.
当Sunshine 被启动后，我们希望我们的用户能够
When Sunshine is launched, we want our users to be immediately greeted with up
立刻看到数据，而不是一个空白页面
to date hot off the API weather information and not a blank screen.
app的速度越快，用的人越多
The faster people can use an app, the more it will be used.
比如天气，人们想立刻看到尽可能多的细节
For something like weather, people want the details immediately available.
其次，使用任何无线电有损于设备的电池寿命
Second, using any radio is detrimental to the battery life of the device,
尤其是蜂窝无线电
especially the cellular radio.
存储气象数据，而不是每次都获取数据，
Storing the weather data rather than fetching it each time saves
可以节省电池寿命
battery life.
这会让用户更快乐
And that leads to happier users.
第三，有很多用户会计算数据流量
Third, there are many users on metered data plans or
或者用户可能会使用漫游当他们想使用Sunshine的时候
users may be roaming when they want to use Sunshine.
所有这些不必要的数据可能积少成多
All those unnecessary data fetches can add up.
第四，如果你的app 正在运行一个web 服务
Fourth, if you're running a web service for your application,
你会非常愿意去降低服务器负载以及网络带宽
you'll be highly motivated to reduce the server load and network bandwidth.
第五，仍然有很多地方，
Fifth, there are still lots of places that don't
没有一个持续稳定的网络连接
have a network connection available constantly.
app的一个首要优势就是可以抵抗恶劣的网络状况
One of the prime advantages of having a mobile app is being resistant to bad or
或者不存在的网络状况
non-existent network conditions.
第六，最后的是，你永远不知道你的用户在哪里使用你的app
Sixth, and finally, you never know where a user will want to use your app.
尽管我们的天气 api 目前还不支持外太空定位
Although our weather API currently doesn't support outer space locations.
聪明的做法是，我们使用系统资源是让
Being smart about the way we use system resources is key to making the Sunshine
Sunshine 成为一个好的Android 公民的关键
a good Android citizen.
作为一个有良心的开发者，我们努力是我们所有的应用都遵守
As conscientious developers, we strive to make all of our apps adhere to these
最大限度的减少网络请求
principles by minimizing network activity and
并且可以在有网和没有网的状态下无缝连接的原则
working seamlessly between offline and online states.
我们持久化Sunshine的数据，以提供更好的用户体验
We persist data in Sunshine to make it both a better experience for
更少的网络请求，更少的耗电！
users, while making it use less network and battery resources.